<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Arbortext, Inc., 1988-2014, v.4002-->
<!DOCTYPE dmodule [
<!ENTITY % ISOEntities PUBLIC "ISO 8879-1986//ENTITIES ISO Character Entities 20030531//EN//XML" "http://www.s1000d.org/S1000D_2-3/ent/xml/ISOEntities">
%ISOEntities;
]>
<dmodule
xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="http://www.s1000d.org/S1000D_4-1/xml_schema_flat/descript.xsd"
xmlns:dc="http://www.purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
<identAndStatusSection>
<dmAddress>
<dmIdent>
<dmCode assyCode="00" disassyCode="00" disassyCodeVariant="A" infoCode="010" infoCodeVariant="A" itemLocationCode="C" modelIdentCode="HONAERO" subSubSystemCode="0" subSystemCode="0" systemCode="00" systemDiffCode="EAA"/>
<language countryIsoCode="US" languageIsoCode="sx"/>
<issueInfo inWork="01" issueNumber="001"/></dmIdent>
<dmAddressItems>
<issueDate day="01" month="09" year="2019"/>
<dmTitle><techName>LRU</techName><infoName>LICENSE AGREEMENT</infoName>
</dmTitle>
</dmAddressItems></dmAddress>
<dmStatus issueType="new">
<security securityClassification="01"/>
<responsiblePartnerCompany enterpriseCode="58960">
</responsiblePartnerCompany>
<originator enterpriseCode="58960"></originator>
<applic id="app-0001a">
<displayText>
<simplePara>ALL</simplePara>
</displayText>
</applic>
<brexDmRef><dmRef><dmRefIdent><dmCode assyCode="00" disassyCode="00"
disassyCodeVariant="A" infoCode="022" infoCodeVariant="A"
itemLocationCode="D" modelIdentCode="HONAERO" subSubSystemCode="0"
subSystemCode="0" systemCode="00" systemDiffCode="A"/></dmRefIdent></dmRef></brexDmRef>
<qualityAssurance><firstVerification verificationType="tabtop"/></qualityAssurance>
</dmStatus>
</identAndStatusSection>
<content><description>
<levelledPara><title>HONEYWELL MATERIALS LICENSE AGREEMENT</title>
<para>This document and the information contained herein (&ldquo;the
Materials&rdquo;) are the proprietary data of Honeywell. These Materials
are provided for the exclusive use of Honeywell-authorized Service
Centers; Honeywell-authorized repair facilities; owners of a Honeywell
aerospace product that is the subject of these Materials (&ldquo;Honeywell
Product&rdquo;) that have entered into a written agreement with Honeywell
relating to the repair or maintenance of Honeywell Product; and direct
recipients of Materials from Honeywell via https://aerospace.honeywell.com/en/learn/about-us/about-myaerospace
that own a Honeywell Product. The terms and conditions of this Honeywell
Materials License Agreement (&ldquo;License Agreement&rdquo;) govern
your use of these Materials, except to the extent that any terms and
conditions of another applicable agreement with Honeywell regarding
the maintenance or repair of a Honeywell Product and that is the subject
of the Materials conflict with the terms and conditions of this License
Agreement, in which case the terms and conditions of the other agreement
will govern. However, this License Agreement will govern in the event
of a conflict between these terms and conditions and those of a purchase
order or acknowledgement. Your access or use of the Materials represents
your acceptance of the terms of this License Agreement.</para>
<levelledPara><para>License Grant - If you are a party to an applicable
written agreement with Honeywell relating to the repair or maintenance
of the subject Honeywell Product, subject to your compliance with
the terms and conditions of this License Agreement, Honeywell hereby
grants you, and you accept, a limited, personal, non-transferable,
non-exclusive license to use these Materials only in accordance with
that agreement.</para>
<para>If you are a direct recipient of these Materials from Honeywell&rsquo;s
MyAerospace Technical Publication website and are not a party to an
agreement related to the maintenance or repair of the subject Honeywell
Product, subject to your compliance with the terms and conditions
of this License Agreement, Honeywell hereby grants you, and you accept,
a limited, personal, non-transferable, non-exclusive license to use
a single copy of these Materials to maintain or repair only the subject
Honeywell Product installed or intended to be installed on the aircraft
you own and/or operate and only at the facility to which these Materials
have been shipped (&ldquo;the Licensed Facility&rdquo;). Transfer
of the Materials to another facility owned by you is permitted only
if the original Licensed Facility retains no copies of the Materials,
the transferee accepts all of your obligations and liabilities under
this License Agreement, and you provide prior written notice to Honeywell
with the name and address of the transferee. You agree not to use
these Materials for commercial purposes.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>Restrictions on Use - You may not sell, rent,
lease, or (except as authorized under any applicable airworthiness
authority regulation) lend the Materials to anyone for any purpose.
You may not use the Materials to reverse engineer any Honeywell product,
hardware or software, and may not decompile or disassemble software
provided under this License Agreement, except and only to the extent
that such activity is expressly permitted by applicable law notwithstanding
this limitation. You may not create derivative works or modify the
Materials in any way. You agree that Materials shall only be used
for the purpose of the rights granted herein. The Material furnished
hereunder may be subject to U.S. export regulations. You will adhere
to all U.S. export regulations as published and released from time
to time by the U.S. Government. You may not design or manufacture
a Honeywell part or detail of a Honeywell part, to create a repair
for a Honeywell part, design or manufacture any part that is similar
or identical to a Honeywell part, compare a Honeywell part or design
of a Honeywell part to another part design, or apply for FAA PMA or
other domestic or foreign governmental approval to manufacture or
repair a Honeywell part.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>Rights In Materials - Honeywell retains all rights
in these Materials and in any copies thereof that are not expressly
granted to you, including all rights in patents, copyrights, trademarks,
and trade secrets. The Materials are licensed and not sold under this
License Agreement. No license to use any Honeywell trademarks or patents
is granted under this License Agreement.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>Changes - Honeywell reserves the right to change
the terms and conditions of this License Agreement at any time, including
the right to change or impose charges for continued use of the Materials.
Honeywell may add, delete or otherwise modify any portion of the Materials
(&ldquo;Updated Materials&rdquo;) at any time. You agree to stop using
outdated Materials upon issuance of any Updated Materials.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>Confidentiality - You acknowledge that these Materials
contain information that is confidential and proprietary to Honeywell.
You agree to take all reasonable efforts to maintain the confidentiality
of these Materials.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>Assignment And Transfer - This License Agreement
may be assigned to a service center approved and formally designated
as a service center by Honeywell, provided, however, that you retain
no copies of the Materials in whole or in part. However, the recipient
of any such assignment or transfer must assume all of your obligations
and liabilities under this License Agreement. No assignment or transfer
shall relieve any party of any obligation that such party then has
hereunder. Otherwise, neither this License Agreement nor any rights,
licenses or privileges granted under this License Agreement, nor any
of its duties or obligations hereunder, nor any interest or proceeds
in and to the Materials shall be assignable or transferable (in insolvency
proceedings, by merger, by operation of law, by purchase, by change
of control or otherwise) by you without Honeywell&rsquo;s written
consent.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>Copies of Materials - Unless you have the express
written permission of Honeywell, you may not make or permit making
of copies, digital or printed, of the Materials. You agree to return
the Materials and any such copies thereof to Honeywell upon the request
of Honeywell.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>Term - This License Agreement is effective until
terminated as set forth herein. This License Agreement will terminate
immediately, without notice from Honeywell, if you fail to comply
with any provision of this License Agreement or will terminate simultaneously
with the termination or expiration of your applicable agreement with
Honeywell relating to the repair or maintenance of the subject Honeywell
Product. Upon termination of this License Agreement, you will return
these Materials to Honeywell without retaining any copies, in whole
or in part, and will have one of your authorized officers certify
that all Materials have been returned with no copies retained.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>Audit Rights - Honeywell, through its authorized
representatives, with no less than thirty (30) calendar days notice
from Honeywell, has the right during normal business hours during
the term of this License Agreement and for three (3) years thereafter
to visit you and have access to the inside and outside of your facility
for the purpose of inspecting, observing and evaluating your compliance
under this License Agreement.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>Remedies - Honeywell reserves the right to pursue
all available remedies and damages resulting from a breach of this
License Agreement.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>Limitation of Liability - Honeywell makes no representations
or warranties regarding the use or sufficiency of the Materials. THERE
ARE NO OTHER WARRANTIES, WHETHER WRITTEN OR ORAL, EXPRESS, IMPLIED
OR STATUTORY, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO (i) WARRANTIES ARISING
FROM COURSE OF PERFORMANCE, DEALING, USAGE, OR TRADE, WHICH ARE HEREBY
EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMED, OR (ii) WARRANTIES AGAINST INFRINGEMENT OF INTELLECTUAL
PROPERTY RIGHTS OF THIRD PARTIES, EVEN IF HONEYWELL HAS BEEN ADVISED
OF ANY SUCH INFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT WILL HONEYWELL BE LIABLE FOR
ANY INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, SPECIAL DAMAGES, INDIRECT
DAMAGES, LOSS OF PROFITS, LOSS OF REVENUES, OR LOSS OF USE, EVEN IF
INFORMED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. TO THE EXTENT PERMITTED
BY APPLICABLE LAW, THESE LIMITATIONS AND EXCLUSIONS WILL APPLY REGARDLESS
OF WHETHER LIABILITY ARISES FROM BREACH OF CONTRACT, WARRANTY, INDEMNITY,
TORT (INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO NEGLIGENCE), BY OPERATION OF LAW,
OR OTHERWISE.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>Controlling Law - This License Agreement shall
be governed and construed in accordance with the laws of the State
of New York without regard to the conflict of laws provisions thereof.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>Severability - In the event any provision of this
License Agreement is determined to be illegal, invalid, or unenforceable,
the validity and enforceability of the remaining provisions of this
License Agreement will not be affected and, in lieu of such illegal,
invalid, or unenforceable provision, there will be added as part of
this License Agreement one or more provisions as similar in terms
as may be legal, valid and enforceable under controlling law.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>Integration and Modification - This License Agreement
and all attachments set forth the entire agreement and understanding
between the parties on the subject matter of the License Agreement
and merges all prior discussions and negotiations among them. This
License Agreement may be modified only by a duly-authorized representative
of Honeywell.</para>
</levelledPara>
</levelledPara>
</description></content></dmodule>
<?INMEDCLNPRJ A350_CMMs_-_Honeywell?>
<?INMEDBSPATH A350_CMMs_-_Honeywell?>
<?INMEDLNG sx-US?>
