<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Arbortext, Inc., 1988-2014, v.4002-->
<!DOCTYPE dmodule [
<!ENTITY ICN-58960-0000690256-001-01 SYSTEM "Graphics\ICN-58960-0000690256-001-01.cgm" NDATA cgm>
<!ENTITY ICN-58960-0000690257-001-01 SYSTEM "Graphics\ICN-58960-0000690257-001-01.cgm" NDATA cgm>
<!ENTITY % ISOEntities PUBLIC "ISO 8879-1986//ENTITIES ISO Character Entities 20030531//EN//XML" "http://www.s1000d.org/S1000D_2-3/ent/xml/ISOEntities">
%ISOEntities;
<!NOTATION tif SYSTEM "tif">
<!NOTATION cgm SYSTEM "cgm">
]>
<?Pub Inc?>
<dmodule xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="http://www.s1000d.org/S1000D_4-1/xml_schema_flat/descript.xsd" xmlns:dc="http://www.purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
<identAndStatusSection>
<dmAddress>
<dmIdent>
<dmCode assyCode="00" disassyCode="00" disassyCodeVariant="A" infoCode="018" infoCodeVariant="I" itemLocationCode="C" modelIdentCode="HON99193" subSubSystemCode="0" subSystemCode="0" systemCode="00" systemDiffCode="EAA"/>
<language countryIsoCode="US" languageIsoCode="sx"/>
<issueInfo inWork="00" issueNumber="003"/></dmIdent>
<dmAddressItems>
<issueDate day="23" month="05" year="2018"/>
<dmTitle><techName>Gas Turbine Engine Assembly</techName><infoName>Introduction</infoName></dmTitle>
</dmAddressItems></dmAddress>
<dmStatus issueType="new">
<security securityClassification="01"/>
<responsiblePartnerCompany enterpriseCode="HON99"><enterpriseName>HON99193</enterpriseName></responsiblePartnerCompany>
<originator enterpriseCode="99193"></originator>
<applic>
<displayText>
<simplePara>All</simplePara>
</displayText>
</applic>
<brexDmRef><dmRef><dmRefIdent><dmCode assyCode="00" disassyCode="00" disassyCodeVariant="A" infoCode="018" infoCodeVariant="I" itemLocationCode="C" modelIdentCode="HON99193" subSubSystemCode="0" subSystemCode="0" systemCode="00" systemDiffCode="EAA"/>
</dmRefIdent></dmRef></brexDmRef>
<qualityAssurance>
<unverified/></qualityAssurance></dmStatus>
</identAndStatusSection>
<content><description>
<levelledPara><title>Detailed Parts List</title>
<note>
<notePara>Refer to <internalRef internalRefId="DPLdetailedPartsListExample-AC5996DC" internalRefTargetType="irtt01"></internalRef>.</notePara>
</note>
<levelledPara><para>An item number is given to each part in the DPL and on the related illustration.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>To find a part number in the DPL.</para>
<levelledPara><para>If the part number is known, refer to the Numerical Index to find the figure and item numbers in the DPL.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>If the part number is not known, turn to the illustration; locate the part, and record the item number. The part number is shown opposite the item number in the DPL.</para>
</levelledPara>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>Revision codes of added, changed, or deleted data.</para>
<levelledPara><para>Revision bars in the left margin adjacent to an entry shows changed or added data to the part in the DPL.</para>
</levelledPara>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>Figure item column.</para>
<levelledPara><para>A part not shown on the illustration is identified in the DPL as non-illustrated by a dash (-) before the item number.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>When two or more items that are visually alike are listed in sequence, only the first item is illustrated. The illustration, however, is applicable to both items.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>When components of an assembly or installation are separately illustrated, the assembled item is not illustrated.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>Non-illustrated items may also include shipping covers and plugs, repair kits, or similar items.</para>
</levelledPara>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>Part number column.</para>
<levelledPara><para>A part number that is prefixed usually indicates a type of part or method of procurement. Examples of these prefixes are AN, MS, and NAS. These standard part numbers may be suffixed by numbers only or numbers and letters. Suffix numbers
usually indicate configuration or design difference. Suffix letters usually indicate material, color, or finish differences.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>All procurable components manufactured by Honeywell have a part number. The part number is stamped, etched, or cast on the part at time of manufacture when size, space, or shape is available. More manufacturing symbol(s), letter(s),
or number(s) can be shown with the part number to identify a manufacturing process, a design change, or for a proprietary repair. Do not use this data to order a part. Use only the item part number and nomenclature as shown in the DPL.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>The letter S prefix of a part number designates a Honeywell standard part number. These standard part numbers have suffix letters and numbers.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>Honeywell commercial standard numbers are used in the parts lists to identify off-the-shelf items procured from another manufacturer. A commercial standard number can be a ten or eleven digit number.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>Nonprocurable part numbers are usually easy to identify and are primarily used for information purposes. The part numbers NONPROCXXX, ORDERNHA, GAREFXXX, TUCREFXXX, AIREFXXX, and TORREFXXX are not procurable and should not be ordered.</para>
<levelledPara><para>The part number NONPROCXXX is primarily used to sub-divide components into a logical, easy to use, subgroup. The subgroup is not procurable, but is used to identify a group of procurable components.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>The part number ORDERNHA (Order Next Higher Assembly) is primarily used to identify nonprocurable details of an assembly.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>The part number GAREFXXX, TUCREFXXX, AIREFXXX, and TORREFXXX is used when a procurable part number exceeds 15 digits. When the part number GAREFXXX, TUCREFXXX, AIREFXXX, and TORREFXXX appears in the PART NUMBER column, refer to the
nomenclature for the actual part number of the item desired.</para>
</levelledPara>
</levelledPara>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>Airline stock number column.</para>
<levelledPara><para>The airline stock number column has space for customers to use.</para>
</levelledPara>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>Nomenclature column.</para>
<levelledPara><para>The indenture code shows the relationship of each item to its NHA.</para>
<levelledPara><para>Each item goes in the nomenclature column one indenture (one dot) to the right of the assembly to which it belongs.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>The items at the same indenture are all components of a single assembly or subassembly. Refer to <internalRef internalRefId="figure-112621234-AC57872B" internalRefTargetType="irtt01"></internalRef> for an example of the indenture
code system.</para>
</levelledPara>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>Wherever possible, abbreviations will agree with the ASME Y14.38 specification. The non-standard abbreviations that spell words are not used.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>The vendor code data are as follows:</para>
<levelledPara><para>The vendors with a code number have the letter V before the number. CAGE codes and manufacturers&rsquo; addresses are available at https://cage.dla.mil.</para>
</levelledPara><?Pub Caret 147?>
<levelledPara><para>No vendor code is shown in the nomenclature column of the DPL if the item is a U.S. standard part or Honeywell is the vendor.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>The vendors with no code number (NCN) are identified by (VNCN__).</para>
</levelledPara>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>A Honeywell Specification drawing number will be shown if applicable.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>Refer to this list of possible explanation terms. These terms may be abbreviated.</para>
<levelledPara><para>OPTIONAL shows that the part is an optional alternative to other parts in the same item number variant group.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>ALTERNATE shows that the part is an alternative to other parts in the same item number variant group.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>SUPERSEDED BY shows that the part is replaced by the part number or item number shown and is not interchangeable.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>SUPERSEDES shows that the part replaces the part number or item number shown and is not interchangeable.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>REPLACED BY shows that the part is replaced by the part number or item number shown and is interchangeable. Part can be used until the supply is gone.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>REPLACES shows that the part replaces the part number or item number shown and is interchangeable.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>PRE SERVICE BULLETIN XXXX shows that the part is used if service bulletin XXXX was not done.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>POST SERVICE BULLETIN XXXX shows that the part is used if service bulletin XXXX was done.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>PRE SPARE PARTS BULLETIN XXXX shows that the part is used if spare parts bulletin XXXX was not done.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>POST SPARE PARTS BULLETIN XXXX shows that the part is used if spare parts bulletin XXXX was done.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>NONREPAIRABLE shows that the part cannot be repaired.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>NONPROCURABLE shows that the part or assembled parts cannot be purchased and no part number exists for the assembly. The components of the assembled parts can be ordered unless differently specified.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>ORDER NEXT HIGHER ASSEMBLY shows that the part number is part of a matched set and cannot be ordered independently. The next higher assembly can be ordered.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>REFERENCE (GAREF, TUCREF, AIREF, TORREF, etc.) shows the procurable part number that exceeds 15 digits in the NOMENCLATURE column as ORDER PN NNNN.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>ORDER PART NUMBER shows a nonstandard or reference part number.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>PART ADDED shows the part is added with no comparable component involved in the change. Interchangeability of other parts is not affected by the additions, unless specified.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>DELETED shows the part is not available for use.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>SEE FIGURE FOR DETAILS shows the part number details in a different figure.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>SEE FIGURE FOR NEXT HIGHER ASSEMBLY refers the part number to the next higher assembly.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>USE WITH (ITEM or PART NUMBER) shows a part is used with a different part.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>COMPONENT OF (ITEM or PART NUMBER) shows that the part is a component of a different part.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>MAY BE SUBSTITUTED shows that the part in the NOMENCLATURE column with its vendor code is an equivalent alternative for the part in the PART NUMBER column.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>REFER TO ATA or PUBLICATION NUMBER identifies the assemblies that have their own Component Maintenance Manuals.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>Control Source Drawing (CSD) shows the Honeywell drawing number for the part in the PART NUMBER column.</para>
</levelledPara>
</levelledPara>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>Service bulletin incorporation.</para>
<levelledPara><para>The part numbers deleted by service bulletins and not replaced include the term (DELETED BY SB-NNNN) in the NOMENCLATURE column.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>The part numbers added by service bulletins and that are not replacement parts include the term (ADDED BY SB-NNNN) in the NOMENCLATURE column.</para>
</levelledPara>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>The effectivity code column.</para>
<levelledPara><para>The effectivity code identifies the different configurations of the top assembly in each DPL figure.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>If this column is empty, the part is used in all configurations of the top assembly for that DPL figure.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>If this column has a letter code in it, the part is only used in the configuration of the top assembly that has the same letter code.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>If this column has more than one letter code, the part is used in each top assembly with the same letter codes.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>If a comma separates the column entry (A, C), the other codes do not apply. For example, a component coded A, C is applicable for Codes A and C only and not applicable for Code B.</para>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>If a dash separates the column entry (A-C), the other codes do apply. For example, a component coded A-C is applicable for Codes A, B, and C.</para>
</levelledPara>
</levelledPara>
<levelledPara><para>The units per assembly column.</para>
<levelledPara><para>The units per assembly column show the quantity of parts necessary in the assembly of one next higher assembly. The letters AR in this column show as required items and refer to bulk items or adjustable quantity items, such as shims
or spacers. The letters RF are used to show an item that is shown in another area with a quantity.</para>
<figure id="DPLdetailedPartsListExample-AC5996DC">
<title>DPL Example</title>
<graphic infoEntityIdent="ICN-58960-0000690256-001-01"></graphic>
<legend>
<definitionList><definitionListItem>
<listItemTerm>1</listItemTerm>
<listItemDefinition><para>FIGURE/ITEM column</para>
</listItemDefinition>
</definitionListItem><definitionListItem>
<listItemTerm>2</listItemTerm>
<listItemDefinition><para>PART NUMBER column</para>
</listItemDefinition>
</definitionListItem><definitionListItem>
<listItemTerm>3</listItemTerm>
<listItemDefinition><para>AIRLINE STOCK NUMBER column</para>
</listItemDefinition>
</definitionListItem><definitionListItem>
<listItemTerm>4</listItemTerm>
<listItemDefinition><para>NOMENCLATURE column</para>
</listItemDefinition>
</definitionListItem><definitionListItem>
<listItemTerm>5</listItemTerm>
<listItemDefinition><para>EFFECTIVITY (USE) CODE column</para>
</listItemDefinition>
</definitionListItem><definitionListItem>
<listItemTerm>6</listItemTerm>
<listItemDefinition><para>UNITS PER ASSEMBLY column</para>
</listItemDefinition>
</definitionListItem><definitionListItem>
<listItemTerm>7</listItemTerm>
<listItemDefinition><para>OPTIONAL example</para>
</listItemDefinition>
</definitionListItem><definitionListItem>
<listItemTerm>8</listItemTerm>
<listItemDefinition><para>ALTERNATE example</para>
</listItemDefinition>
</definitionListItem><definitionListItem>
<listItemTerm>9</listItemTerm>
<listItemDefinition><para>SUPERSEDED BY example</para>
</listItemDefinition>
</definitionListItem><definitionListItem>
<listItemTerm>10</listItemTerm>
<listItemDefinition><para>SUPERSEDES example</para>
</listItemDefinition>
</definitionListItem><definitionListItem>
<listItemTerm>11</listItemTerm>
<listItemDefinition><para>REPLACED BY example</para>
</listItemDefinition>
</definitionListItem><definitionListItem>
<listItemTerm>12</listItemTerm>
<listItemDefinition><para>REPLACES example</para>
</listItemDefinition>
</definitionListItem><definitionListItem>
<listItemTerm>13</listItemTerm>
<listItemDefinition><para>PRE SERVICE BULLETIN example</para>
</listItemDefinition>
</definitionListItem><definitionListItem>
<listItemTerm>14</listItemTerm>
<listItemDefinition><para>POST SERVICE BULLETIN example</para>
</listItemDefinition>
</definitionListItem><definitionListItem>
<listItemTerm>15</listItemTerm>
<listItemDefinition><para>PRE SPARE PARTS BULLETIN example</para>
</listItemDefinition>
</definitionListItem><definitionListItem>
<listItemTerm>16</listItemTerm>
<listItemDefinition><para>POST SPARE PARTS BULLETIN example</para>
</listItemDefinition>
</definitionListItem><definitionListItem>
<listItemTerm>17</listItemTerm>
<listItemDefinition><para>NONREPAIRABLE example</para>
</listItemDefinition>
</definitionListItem><definitionListItem>
<listItemTerm>18</listItemTerm>
<listItemDefinition><para>NONPROCURABLE example</para>
</listItemDefinition>
</definitionListItem><definitionListItem>
<listItemTerm>19</listItemTerm>
<listItemDefinition><para>ORDER NEXT HIGHER ASSEMBLY example</para>
</listItemDefinition>
</definitionListItem><definitionListItem>
<listItemTerm>20</listItemTerm>
<listItemDefinition><para>REFERENCE example</para>
</listItemDefinition>
</definitionListItem><definitionListItem>
<listItemTerm>21</listItemTerm>
<listItemDefinition><para>ORDER PART NUMBER example</para>
</listItemDefinition>
</definitionListItem><definitionListItem>
<listItemTerm>22</listItemTerm>
<listItemDefinition><para>DELETED example</para>
</listItemDefinition>
</definitionListItem><definitionListItem>
<listItemTerm>23</listItemTerm>
<listItemDefinition><para>SEE FIGURE FOR BREAKDOWN example</para>
</listItemDefinition>
</definitionListItem><definitionListItem>
<listItemTerm>24</listItemTerm>
<listItemDefinition><para>SEE FIGURE FOR NEXT HIGHER ASSEMBLY example</para>
</listItemDefinition>
</definitionListItem><definitionListItem>
<listItemTerm>25</listItemTerm>
<listItemDefinition><para>USE WITH (ITEM or PART NUMBER) example</para>
</listItemDefinition>
</definitionListItem><definitionListItem>
<listItemTerm>26</listItemTerm>
<listItemDefinition><para>COMPONENT OF (ITEM or PART NUMBER) example</para>
</listItemDefinition>
</definitionListItem><definitionListItem>
<listItemTerm>27</listItemTerm>
<listItemDefinition><para>Changed or added data indicator example</para>
</listItemDefinition>
</definitionListItem><definitionListItem>
<listItemTerm>28</listItemTerm>
<listItemDefinition><para>Non-illustrated indicator example</para>
</listItemDefinition>
</definitionListItem><definitionListItem>
<listItemTerm>29</listItemTerm>
<listItemDefinition><para>Vendor code example</para>
</listItemDefinition>
</definitionListItem><definitionListItem>
<listItemTerm>30</listItemTerm>
<listItemDefinition><para>Honeywell specification drawing number example</para>
</listItemDefinition>
</definitionListItem><definitionListItem>
<listItemTerm>31</listItemTerm>
<listItemDefinition><para>Effectivity and Use code example</para>
</listItemDefinition>
</definitionListItem><definitionListItem>
<listItemTerm>32</listItemTerm>
<listItemDefinition><para>Quantity example</para>
</listItemDefinition>
</definitionListItem><definitionListItem>
<listItemTerm>33</listItemTerm>
<listItemDefinition><para>RF indicates item referenced elsewhere</para>
</listItemDefinition>
</definitionListItem><definitionListItem>
<listItemTerm>34</listItemTerm>
<listItemDefinition><para>As required example</para>
</listItemDefinition>
</definitionListItem></definitionList>
</legend>
</figure>
<?Pub _newpage?>
<figure id="figure-112621234-AC57872B">
<title>Nomenclature Indentures</title>
<graphic infoEntityIdent="ICN-58960-0000690257-001-01"></graphic>
</figure>
</levelledPara>
</levelledPara>
</levelledPara>
</description></content></dmodule>
